Hi, I'm Nicholas Rotz, Senior Partner at
KeyState Capital. We had two talks. The
first was about data registries and the
governance. And the second talk was
investing in the trust spanning protocol,
which is KERI. So the thing we do
differently that differentiates us from
the marketplace is the fact that one,
we're a series of dedicated investors who
have a passion and a vision for what the
space is going to be like. This is shown
in our products like the web of trust map,
verifiable smart contract, as well as
potential designs on governance that this
space desperately needs. So you're not
going to see a more engaged investor in
the KERI ecosystem. If we were never here,
so we're talking about it's a wonderful
life, you know, George Bailey, which she
was never born, that sort of reality.
There would be no QVIs. There would be no
VLEI. There would be no open verifiable
communication. There would be no
provenant. There would be no healthcare
because there would be no one to actually
place the capital for these things to
happen. I'm not saying that we are the sum
total of everything in this ecosystem, but
it did need the catalyst of contribution
that we were willing to put up or shut up
about. So yeah, without us here, we were a
necessary but not sufficient part of the
KERI ecosystem.